<resources>
    <string
        name="app_name">Anime List RV
    </string>

    <string-array name="anime_name">
        <item>
            1. Dragon Ball
        </item>
        <item>
            2. Naruto
        </item>
        <item>
            3. Rurouni Kenshin
        </item>
        <item>
            4. Bleach
        </item>
        <item>
            5. One Piece
        </item>
        <item>
            6. Boku No Hero Academia
        </item>
        <item>
            7. Kimetsu No Yaiba
        </item>
        <item>
            8. Fairy Tail
        </item>
        <item>
            9. Dr. Stone
        </item>
        <item>
            10. Death Note
        </item>
        <item>
            11. Cowboy Bebop
        </item>
        <item>
            12. Assassination Classroom
        </item>
        <item>
            13. One Punch Man
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="anime_status">
        <item>
            1. Ongoing
        </item>
        <item>
            2. Finished
        </item>
        <item>
            3. Finished
        </item>
        <item>
            4. Finished
        </item>
        <item>
            5. Ongoing
        </item>
        <item>
            6. Ongoing
        </item>
        <item>
            7. Ongoing
        </item>
        <item>
            8. Finished
        </item>
        <item>
            9. Ongoing
        </item>
        <item>
            10. Finished
        </item>
        <item>
            11. Finished
        </item>
        <item>
            12. Finished
        </item>
        <item>
            13. Ongoing
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="DB">
        <item>
            Dragon Ball
        </item>
        <item>
            The Dragon Ball story takes place on Earth where Goku goes on adventures to find the
            Dragon Balls, as well as aspiring to become a great fighter, and compete in multiple
            martial arts tournaments. Goku later stops the evil Red Ribbon Army, then 3 years later,
            thwarts the plans of Grand Demon King Piccolo for world conquest, afterwards he and his
            friends protect the Earth from the Saiyan invasion. The setting also goes to Planet
            Namek later on in the series for Bulma, Gohan, and Krillin to revive fallen
            friends of Goku from the attack of Saiyans, where they encounter higher ups of Vegeta,
            as well as the cosmic emperor, Freeza.
        </item>
        <item>
            Release Date: April 26, 1989
        </item>
        <item>
            Total Episodes: 835 (till date)
        </item>
        <item>
            Main Characters: Goku, Bulma, Vegeta
        </item>
        <item>
            Voice Acts: Masako Nozawa, Hiromi Tsuru, Ryo Horikawa
        </item>
        <item>
            Company: Toei Animations
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="NRT">
        <item>
            Naruto
        </item>
        <item>
            A powerful fox known as the Nine-Tails attacks Konoha, the hidden leaf village in the
            Land of Fire, one of the Five Great Shinobi Countries in the Ninja World. In response,
            the leader of Konoha and the Fourth Hokage, Minato Namikaze (with his wife Kushina
            Uzumaki) seals the fox inside the body of his newborn son, Naruto Uzumaki, making
            Naruto a host of the beast; this costs the life of the Father of Naruto, and the Third
            Hokage returns from retirement to become leader of Konoha again. Naruto is often
            ridiculed by the Konoha villagers for being the host of the Nine-Tails. Because of a
            decree made by the Third Hokage forbidding anyone to mention these events, Naruto knows
            nothing about the Nine-Tails until 12 years later, when Mizuki, a renegade ninja,
            reveals the truth to Naruto. Naruto then defeats Mizuki in combat, earning the respect
            of his teacher Iruka Umino.
        </item>
        <item>
            Release Date: October 3, 2002
        </item>
        <item>
            Total Episodes: 720
        </item>
        <item>
            Main Characters: Naruto, Sasuke, Sakura
        </item>
        <item>
            Voice Acts: Junko Takeuchi, Noriaki Sugiyama, Chie Nakamura
        </item>
        <item>
            Company: Pierrot
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="RK">
        <item>
            Rurouni Kenshin
        </item>
        <item>
            In the early Meiji era, after participating in the Bakumatsu war as the assassin
            "Hitokiri Battōsai", Himura Kenshin wanders the countryside of Japan with a reverse
            blade katana, offering protection and aid to those in need as atonement for the murders
            he once committed. When arriving in Tokyo in the 11th year of Meiji (1878), he meets a
            young woman named Kamiya Kaoru, who is in the middle of a fight with a murderer - who
            claims to be the Hitokiri Battōsai - tarnishing the name of the swordsmanship school
            that she teaches. Kenshin decides to help her and defeats the fake Battōsai. After
            discovering that Kenshin is the real infamous assassin, Kaoru offers him a place to
            stay at her dojo noting that he is peace-loving and not cold-hearted, as his reputation
            implies. Kenshin accepts and begins to establish lifelong relationships with many
            people such as Sagara Sanosuke, a former Sekihō Army member; Myōjin Yahiko, an orphan
            from a samurai family who is also living with Kaoru as her student.
        </item>
        <item>
            Release Date: January 10, 1996
        </item>
        <item>
            Total Episodes: 95
        </item>
        <item>
            Main Characters: Kenshin, Kaoru, Sanosuke, Yahiko
        </item>
        <item>
            Voice Acts: Mayo Sukukaze, Miki Fujitani, Yuji Ueda, Miina Tominaga
        </item>
        <item>
            Company: Studio Gallop
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="BLCH">
        <item>
            Bleach
        </item>
        <item>
            In Karakura Town, a 15-year-old high school student Ichigo Kurosaki becomes a
            substitute Soul Reaper when Rukia Kuchiki, a Soul Reaper, cannot fulfill her duties
            after engaging in battle with a particularly powerful Hollow. Although initially
            reluctant to accept the heavy responsibility, he begins eliminating Hollows in place of
            Rukia and during this time discovers that several of his friends and classmates are
            spiritually aware and have powers of their own: Uryu Ishida is a Quincy who can use
            spirit particles, Orihime Inoue possesses a group of protective spirits known as the
            Shun Shun Rikka and Yasutora Sado  has strength equal to the Hollows encased in his
            tough right (and occasionally left) arm.
        </item>
        <item>
            Release Date: October 5, 2004
        </item>
        <item>
            Total Episodes: 366
        </item>
        <item>
            Main Characters: Ichigo, Rukia
        </item>
        <item>
            Voice Acts: Masakazu Morita, Fumiko Orikasa
        </item>
        <item>
            Company: Pierrot
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="OP">
        <item>
            One Piece
        </item>
        <item>
            The adventures of Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body gained the properties of rubber
            after unintentionally eating a Devil Fruit. With his crew of pirates, named the Straw
            Hat Pirates, Luffy explores the Grand Line in search of the ultimate treasure of world
            known as "One Piece" in order to become the next Pirate King.
        </item>
        <item>
            Release Date: October 20, 1999
        </item>
        <item>
            Total Episodes: 951 (till date)
        </item>
        <item>
            Main Characters: Luffy, Zoro, Nami
        </item>
        <item>
            Voice Acts: Mayumi Tanaka, Kazuya Nakai, Akemi Okamura
        </item>
        <item>
            Company: Toei Animations
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="BNHA">
        <item>
            Boku No Hero Academia
        </item>
        <item>
            Izuku Midoriya, a boy born without superpowers in a world where they are the norm, but
            who still dreams of becoming a superhero himself, and is scouted by the greatest hero
            of world who shares his powers with Izuku after recognizing his value and enrolls him
            in a high school for heroes in training.
        </item>
        <item>
            Release Date: April 3, 2016
        </item>
        <item>
            Total Episodes: 88 (till date)
        </item>
        <item>
            Main Characters: Midoriya, Bakugo, Ochako
        </item>
        <item>
            Voice Acts: Daiki Yamashita, Nobuhiko Okamoto, Ayane Sakura
        </item>
        <item>
            Company: Funimation
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="KNY">
        <item>
            Kimetsu No Yaiba
        </item>
        <item>
            Tanjiro Kamado is a kind-hearted and intelligent boy who lives with his family in the
            mountains. He has become sole source of income of his after the passing of his father,
            making trips to the nearby village to sell charcoal. Everything changes when he comes
            home one day to discover that his family has been attacked and slaughtered by a demon.
            Tanjiro and his sister Nezuko are the sole survivors of the incident, with Nezuko being
            transformed into a demon, but still surprisingly showing signs of human emotion and
            thought. After an encounter with Giyu Tomioka, a demon slayer, Tanjiro is recruited by
            Giyu to also become a demon slayer and begins his quest to help his sister turn human
            again and avenge the deaths of the rest of his family.
        </item>
        <item>
            Release Date: April 6, 2019
        </item>
        <item>
            Total Episodes: 26 (till date)
        </item>
        <item>
            Main Characters: Tanjiro, Nezuko
        </item>
        <item>
            Voice Acts: Natsuki Hanae, Akari Kito
        </item>
        <item>
            Company: Ufotable
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="FT">
        <item>
            Fairy Tails
        </item>
        <item>
            The world of Earth-land is home to numerous guilds where wizards apply their magic for
            paid job requests. Natsu Dragneel, a Dragon Slayer wizard from the Fairy Tail guild,
            explores the Kingdom of Fiore in search of his missing adoptive father, the dragon
            Igneel. During his journey, he befriends a young celestial wizard named Lucy Heartfilia
            and invites her to join Fairy Tail. Lucy forms a team with Natsu and his cat-like
            Exceed partner, Happy, which is joined by other guild members: Gray Fullbuster, an ice
            wizard; Erza Scarlet, a magical knight; and Wendy Marvell and Carla, another Dragon
            Slayer and Exceed duo. The team embark on numerous missions together, which include
            subduing criminals, illegal dark guilds, and ancient Etherious demons created by Zeref,
            a wizard cursed with immortality and deadly power.
        </item>
        <item>
            Release Date: October 12, 2009
        </item>
        <item>
            Total Episodes: 328
        </item>
        <item>
            Main Characters: Natsu, Lucy
        </item>
        <item>
            Voice Acts: Tetsuya Kakihara, Aya Hirano
        </item>
        <item>
            Company: A-1 Pictures
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="DS">
        <item>
            Dr. Stone
        </item>
        <item>
            Beginning in April 5738 A.D., it has been over 3,700 years since a mysterious flash of
            light petrified nearly all human life. A 16-year-old genius named Senku Ishigami is
            suddenly revived to find himself in a world where all traces of human civilization have
            been eroded by time. Senku sets up a base-camp and begins to study the petrified humans
            in order to determine the cause of the event, as well as a cure.
        </item>
        <item>
            Release Date: July 5, 2019
        </item>
        <item>
            Total Episodes: 24 (till date)
        </item>
        <item>
            Main Characters: Senku, Taiju, Yuzuriha
        </item>
        <item>
            Voice Acts: Yusuke Kobayashi, Makoto Furukawa, Kana Ichinose
        </item>
        <item>
            Company: TMS/8PAN
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="DN">
        <item>
            Death Note
        </item>
        <item>
            In Tokyo, an intelligent yet disaffected high-school student named Light Yagami finds
            the "Death Note", a mysterious black notebook which can kill anyone as long as the user
            knows both the name and face of the targets. After verifying that the notebook works and
            initially being terrified of its god-like abilities, Light begins to consider the
            possibilities of the Death Note abilities and sets out to create a utopian world
            without crime, killing numerous high-profile Japanese criminals, before eventually
            targeting international criminals and felons around the world. Five days after
            discovering the notebook, Light is visited by Ryuk, a "Shinigami", beings inspired by
            the Japanese god of death and the previous owner of Death Note. Ryuk, who is invisible
            to anyone who has not touched the Death Note, reveals that he dropped the notebook into
            the human world out of boredom and is amused by the actions of Light.
        </item>
        <item>
            Release Date: October 3, 2006
        </item>
        <item>
            Total Episodes: 37
        </item>
        <item>
            Main Characters: Light, L
        </item>
        <item>
            Voice Acts: Mamoru Miyano, Kappei Yamaguchi
        </item>
        <item>
            Company: Mad House
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="CB">
        <item>
            Cowboy Bebop
        </item>
        <item>
            In 2071, roughly fifty years after an accident with a hyperspace gateway made the Earth
            almost uninhabitable, humanity has colonized most of the rocky planets and moons of the
            Solar System. Amid a rising crime rate, the Inter Solar System Police (ISSP) set up a
            legalized contract system, in which registered bounty hunters (also referred to as
            "Cowboys") chase criminals and bring them in alive in return for a reward. The series
            protagonists are bounty hunters working from the spaceship Bebop.
        </item>
        <item>
            Release Date: April 3, 1998
        </item>
        <item>
            Total Episodes: 26
        </item>
        <item>
            Main Characters: Jet, Spike, Faye, Edward
        </item>
        <item>
            Voice Acts: Unsho Ishizuka, Koichi Yamadera, Megumi Hayashibara, Aoi Tada
        </item>
        <item>
            Company: Sunrise
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="AC">
        <item>
            Assassination Classroom
        </item>
        <item>
            Earth is left in jeopardy after an immensely powerful tentacled creature suddenly
            appears and destroys 70% of the moon, leaving it permanently in the shape of a crescent.
            The organism claims that within a year he will destroy the planet next, but offers
            mankind a chance to avert this fate. In class 3-E, the End Class of Kunugigaoka Junior
            High School, he starts working as a homeroom teacher where he teaches his students
            regular subjects, as well as the ways of assassination. The Japanese government
            promises a reward of ¥10 billion to whoever among the students succeeds in killing the
            organism, whom they have named "Koro-sensei" . However, this proves to be a highly
            unachievable task, as not only does he have several superpowers at his disposal,
            including accelerated regeneration, visual cloning, an invincible form, and the ability
            to move and fly at Mach 20, but he is also the best teacher they could ask for, helping
            them to improve their grades, individual skills, and prospects for the future.
        </item>
        <item>
            Release Date: January 9, 2015
        </item>
        <item>
            Total Episodes: 47
        </item>
        <item>
            Main Characters: Koro, Nagisa, Karma
        </item>
        <item>
            Voice Acts: Jun Fukuyama, Mai Fuchigami, Nobuhiko Okamoto
        </item>
        <item>
            Company: Funimation
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="OPM">
        <item>
            One Punch Man
        </item>
        <item>
            On a supercontinent Earth, powerful monsters and villains have been wreaking havoc in
            the cities. In response, the millionaire Agoni creates the Hero Association, which
            employs superheroes to fight evil. Saitama, an unassociated hero, hails from City Z and
            performs heroic deeds for his own enjoyment. He has trained himself to the point of
            being able to defeat any enemy with a single punch, but his unmatched strength has left
            him with an overwhelming sense of boredom.
        </item>
        <item>
            Release Date: December 4, 2015
        </item>
        <item>
            Total Episodes: 24 (till date)
        </item>
        <item>
            Main Characters: Saitama, Genos
        </item>
        <item>
            Voice Acts: Makoto Furukawa, Kaito Ishikawa
        </item>
        <item>
            Company: Mad House
        </item>
    </string-array>

</resources>